Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  - Stan Healy's Cadillac with house, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1688)
  - Stan Healy's Thunderbird, 1956 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1689)
  - KYSS Car Unit #91 (Jim Goodrich's car), undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1690)
  - Three KYSS cars overlooking Missoua, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1691)
  - Three KYSS cars overlooking Missoua, including 99, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1692)
  - Sherman Adams at the Missoula County Airport, 1956 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1693)
  - Ground view of entrance to Missoula County Airport, 1951 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1694)
  - Missoula County Airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1695)
  - Interior of Johnson-Bell terminal, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1696)
  - 35mm airport scenes; interior and outside of Johnson-Bell airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1697)
  - 35mm airport scenes: interior and outside of Johnson-Bell airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1698)
  - Johnson-Bell airport tower, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1699)
  - Sherman Adams at the Missoula County Airport, 1956 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1700)
  - Sherman Adams at the Missoula County Airport, 1956 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1701)
  - Ground view of airplane and aerial view of aerial fire depot, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1702)
  - Man working on tail of airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1703)
  - Men working on airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1704)
  - Men working on airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1705)
  - Men working on skids of airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1706)
  - Men building a hanger at the airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1707)
  - Men building a hanger at the airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1708)
  - Man refueling airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1710)
  - Emergency landed F-86 Sabre, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1711)
  - Belly landed Air Force Jet, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1714)
  - Montana Legion at airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1720)
  - Airplane that lands on water, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1721)
  - Airplane that lands on water, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1722)
  - Airplane that lands on water, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1723)
  - Old Navy Airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1724)
  - Old Navy Airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1725)
  - Old Navy Airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1726)
  - Old Navy Airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1727)
  - Old Navy Airplane, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1728)
  - Airplanes leaving a hanger at the airport, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1730)
  - Airplanes coming out of a hanger, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1731)
  - Aerial view of Johnson-bell field before runway lengthening, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1733)
  - Aerial view of tank farm and railroad on Old Highway 10 leading to airport, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1734)
  - Aerial view of Missoula County Airport and Fire depot, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1735)
  - Aerial view of Missoula County Airport, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1736)
  - Aerial view of tank farm and railroad on Old Highway 10 leading to airport, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1737)
  - Aerial view of aerial fire depot, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1738)
  - Aerial view of Missoula, northside, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1739)
  - Aerial view of Interstate from Northside, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1742)
  - Aerial view of Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1743)
  - Aerial view of Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1744)
  - Aerial view of Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1745)
  - Aerial view of Interstate from Northside, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1746)
  - Aerial view of Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1747)
  - Aerial view of Interstate 90, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1748)
  - Aerial view looking south along Brooks Street from Rose Park, Missoula, Montana, June 27, 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1749A)
  - Aerial view looking south along Brooks Street, Holiday Village in the center of the photograph, Missoula, Montana, circa 1966 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1749B)
  - Tearing down northside for Interstate 90, N.P. Hospital in background, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1750)
  - Tearing down northside for Interstate 90, N.P. Hospital in background, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1751)
  - Tearing down northside for Interstate 90, N.P. Hospital in background, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1752)
  - Tearing down northside for Interstate 90, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1753)
  - Halftime at Montana Grizzly football game, marching band on field, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1754)
  - Night scene on Higgins Avenue near Park Hotel, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1755)
  - Parade on Main Street in Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1756)
  - Main Street, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1757)
  - Parade down Higgins Avenue, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1758)
  - Group of young people preparing the leave on a road trip, near California Ave, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1759)
  - Cars parked on California Ave. before a trip, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1760)
  - Cars parked on California Ave. before a trip, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1761)
  - Higgins Avenue, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1762)
  - Higgins Avenue, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1763)
  - Western Clothing Store, Corner of Spruce and Higgins, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1764)
  - Old Boat Ferry across the Clark Fork River, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1765)
  - Old Missoula school, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1766)
  - Washington School, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1767)
  - Hellgate High School, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1768)
  - Old Missoula grade school, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1769)
  - Central Schools, 1950s (Box 5, Photo number 90-1770)
  - Trees on a field in Missoula, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1771)
  - Trees on a field in Missoula, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1772)
  - Fence storage near railroad tracks, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1773)
  - Night scene on Higgins Avenue near Hotel Priess, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1774)
  - Moving a building across Higgins Avenue, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1775)
  - View of the future site of the Lincold-Russell St. bridge, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1776)
  - Old County Shop for vehicle storage, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1779)
  - Cars crossing the Orange Street bridge, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1780)
  - Luther League parade on Higgins Avenue near Atlantic Hotel, 1957 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1781)
  - Missoula Citizen's Parade South on Higgins Ave., undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1782)
  - Luther League in Missoula, 1958 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1783)
  - Stoverud Jewelry Store next to Hotel Florence, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1784)
  - Stoverud Jewelry Store next to Hotel Florence, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1785)
  - Stan Healy posing with camera on tri-pod, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1786)
  - Stan Healy posing with camera on tri-pod, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1787)
  - Stan Healy portrait with camera, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1788)
  - Stan Healy at work in Missoulian office, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1789)
  - Mrs. Clapp breaking ground at student center on Southwest corner of Maurice, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1790)
  - Mrs. Clapp breaking ground at student center on Southwest corner of Maurice, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1791)
  - University of Montana field house, 1956 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1792)
  - Construction workers near field house at the University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1793)
  - Construction workers near field house at the University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1794)
  - Rec Annex under construction, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1796)
  - Rec Annex under construction, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1797)
  - Field house prior to construction of rec annex, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1798)
  - Foreign Students at the University of Montana, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1799)
  - Looking north toward field house, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1800)
  - Aerial view of music building under construction, University of Montana, 1950s (Box 5, Photo number 90-1801)
  - Chemistry/Pharmacy building under construction, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1802)
  - Chemistry/Pharmacy building under construction, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1803)
  - Business building under constuction, University of Montana, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1804)
  - Business building under constuction, University of Montana, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1805)
  - Business building under constuction, University of Montana, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1806)
  - Construction of the Lodge east of Arthur Avenue, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1807)
  - Construction of the Lodge/Foodservice and Craig Hall, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1808)
  - Turner Hall, Craig/Duniway Hall, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1809)
  - Student Housing and view of Duniway Hall, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1810)
  - Construction of Turner Hall, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1811)
  - Construction of Turner Hall, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1812)
  - Journalism building, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1813)
  - Journalism building, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1814)
  - Journalism building, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1815)
  - Journalism building, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1816)
  - Looking north at the Social Sciences building, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1817)
  - Student housing in Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1818)
  - Tennis courts in front of Aber Hall, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1819)
  - Old ROTC Building, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1820)
  - Old ROTC Building, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1821)
  - Old ROTC Building, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1822)
  - Old ROTC Building, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1823)
  - Old ROTC Building, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1824)
  - Old ROTC Building with Forestry and Journalism buildings, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1825)
  - Old ROTC Building, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1826)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1827)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1828)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1829)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1830)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1831)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1832)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1833)
  - Tearing down Prexy's house at Montana State University (University of Montana), 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1834)
  - Rodeo in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1835)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1836)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1837)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1838)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1839)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1840)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1841)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1842)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1843)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1844)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1845)
  - University of Montana horse show in the fieldhouse, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1846)
  - University drive leading to Main Hall, University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1847)
  - Looking east toward Main Hall, Univeristy of Montana campus, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1849)
  - Aerial view of Main Hall, University of Montana campus, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1850)
  - Aerial view of Main Hall, University of Montana campus, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1851)
  - Construction of Music building, University of Montana campus, 1952 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1852)
  - Halftime in Dornblazer Stadium during University of Montana football game, marching band on field, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1853)
  - Griz football game in old Dornblaser Stadium, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1854)
  - College boys pushing a bell at MSU parade, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1855)
  - MSU parade, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1857)
  - MSU parade, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1858)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1861)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1862)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1863)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1864)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1865)
  - Old John R. Toole Home, now fraternity/sorority house - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1866)
  - Interior of Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1867)
  - Interior of Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1868)
  - Delta Delta Delta House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1869)
  - Delta Delta Delta House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1870)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1871)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1872)
  - Fraternity/Sorority House - University of Montana, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1873)
  - Aerial of Interstate 90 through Missoula, 1963 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1874)
  - Union Hall with Majestic Candy Company on the right, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1875)
  - Union Hall with Majestic Candy Company on the right, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1876)
  - Rodeo at the county fairgrounds, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1877)
  - Fair in Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1878)
  - Aerial view of cemetary next to train tracks, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1879)
  - Aerial view of northside of Missoula and trank tracks west of Higgins Ave, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1880)
  - Aerial view of northwest Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1881)
  - Aerial view of train tracks west of Higgins Ave, Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1882)
  - Aerial view of Missoula north of Clark Fork River, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1883)
  - Aerial view of Missoula north of Clark Fork River, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1884)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1885)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1886)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1887)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1888)
  - Building bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1952 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1889)
  - Building bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1952 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1890)
  - Building bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1952 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1891)
  - Scenes from Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1892)
  - Scenes from Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1893)
  - Scenes from Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1894)
  - Missoula County Fair 4-H building, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1895)
  - Missoula County fair - steam tractor, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1896)
  - Missoula County fair, steam tractor, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1897)
  - Missoula County fair, steam tractor, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1898)
  - Missoula County fair - steam tractor, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1899)
  - Missoula County fair - horse races, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1900)
  - Missoula County fair, horse races, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1901)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1902)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1903)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1904)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1905)
  - Kids around the sheep pen at the Missoula County Fair livestock exhibit, Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1906A)
  - A young boy brushes his sheep at the Missoula County Fair in Missoula, Montana, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1906B)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1907)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1908)
  - Missoula County fair, 1955 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1909)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1910)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1911)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1912)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1913)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1914)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1915)
  - Tearing down bleachers at Missoula County fairgrounds, 1950 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1916)
  - Buildings on the Missoula County fairgrounds, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1918)
  - Buildings on the Missoula County fairgrounds, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1919)
  - Automobile racing event at the Missoula County fairgrounds, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1920)
  - Rose contest at the Missoula County fairgrounds, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1921)
  - Flowers at the Missoula County fair, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1924)
  - Missoula County fairgrounds, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1927)
  - Older people at the Missoula County Fair, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1928)
  - Older people at the Missoula County Fair, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1929)
  - Older people at the Missoula County Fair, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1930)
  - People holding up the Missoula County Fair sign, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1931)
  - Missoula County fair events - Judges of the rose contest, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1932)
  - Stan Healy joining the army, circa 1941 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1933)
  - Stan Healy at the Missoulian office, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1934)
  - Stan Healy at the Missoulian office, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1935)
  - Stan Healy, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1936)
  - Stan Healy with army friend, baby picture, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1937)
  - Stan Healy at the Missoulian office, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1938)
  - Stan Healy at graduation, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1939)
  - Stan Healy in the army, baby picture, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1940)
  - Stan Healy joining the army, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1941)
  - Stan Healy joining the army, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1942)
  - Last man in Montana to be hung - Slim Coleman documentary, 1965 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1943)
  - Old newspaper headlines from the Missoula Sentinel, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1944)
  - An old Northern Pacific Railway train, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1945)
  - Train going up a hill, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1946)
  - Aerial view of Missoula and Roundhouse, 1883 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1947)
  - Aerial view of Missoula and Roundhouse, 1883 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1948)
  - North Coast Limited engine near Drummond, 1909 (Box 5, Photo number 90-1949)
  - Steam engine #42 carrying a load, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1950)
  - Steam locomotive #1536 near Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1951)
  - Steam locomotive #42, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1952)
  - Steam locomotive #1716 at the Continential Divide, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1953)
  - Train used in logging, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1954)
  - Train load of logs, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1955)
  - Passenger train in Missoula, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1956)
  - Steam locomotive in Missoula yard, undated (Box 5, Photo number 90-1957)
  - Steam engine pulling a load, unidentified number, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1959)
  - Freight train, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1960)
  - View of steam engine #2650, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1961)
  - View of steam engine #1844, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1962)
  - Construction of addition to the Northern Pacific Railroad Depot, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1963)
  - Construction of addition onto the Northern Pacific Railway depot, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1964)
  - Old Northern Pacific Railway depot photo with an Northern Pacific Railway train in the background, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1965)
  - Northern Pacific Railway depot with an Northern Pacific Railway train and smokestack in the background, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1966)
  - Old Northern Pacific Railway depot with Northern Pacific Railway train and Northern Pacific Railway smokestack in the background, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1967)
  - Steam engines in winter, plowing through very deep snow, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1968)
  - Old Northern Pacific Railway depot with Northern Pacific Railway train and Northern Pacific Railway smokestack in the background, undated (Box 6, Photo number 90-1969)
  - Northern Pacific Railway yard photo of the coal and waterdeck, 1956 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1970)
  - Northern Pacific Railway yard showing the coal desk and water tower in the background, 1956 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1971A)
  - Northern Pacific passenger cars in the rail yard in Missoula, Montana, August 24, 1956 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1971B)
  - Old steam engine at the Northern Pacific Railway yard, 1956 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1972)
  - Northern Pacific Railway yard showing the watertower, coal deck and an old steam engine, 1956 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1973A)
  - A Northern Pacific Railroad worker pulls a cart through the rail yard at Missoula, Montana; freight train and coal and water deck are in the background, August 24, 1956 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1973B)
  - Northern Pacific Railway depot scene from the C.F. Buls collection, 1921 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1974)
  - Improvements at Missoula Northern Pacific Railway railyard, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1975)
  - Improvements at Missoula Northern Pacific Railway railyard, Missoula, Montana, 1966 (Box 6, Photo number 90-1976)